<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<strings version="0.1">
  <!-- Contents -->
  <contenu_about>
Application thant gives daily prayer times for all known and listed cities worldwide.

Saad Benbouzid © 2010-2011
about.me/saad.benbouzid

Developed using J2ME MIDP 2.0 - CLDC 1.1
Framework (c) Oracle LWUIT

Location data provided by GeoNames.org
  </contenu_about>
  <contenu_consignesGeocoding>
- Type some hints regarding your location and leave blank the inputs you don't want to fill in.
- At least one field has to be filled in.
- The better you fill in the fields, the more accurate will be your result.

If the request returned your desired location, you then have to save the result by selecting "OK".
  </contenu_consignesGeocoding>
  <helpMenuAlerts>
- Select the type of alert and the prayers it pertains to.
- The flash consists in briefly activating the backlight of the phone 5 times in a row.
- If your phone is able to play sound, the local files have to be in WAV or MP3 format.
- For the ringtone or backlight features to run properly when Athan Mobile is closed, the application has to be minimized (and not closed).
- Note that even when the application is minimized, it can stop by itself if the phone may run out of memory resource.
  </helpMenuAlerts>
  <helpMenuCalculationMethod>
- Set your data according to the settings given by your islamic authority and your country.

For further information, please visit the following site :
http://www.salahtimes.com/Web/Pages/FaqAll.aspx
  </helpMenuCalculationMethod>
  <helpMenuCompass>
This window gives you the direction and distance to Mekkah calculated from the location saved in the configuration.
  </helpMenuCompass>
  <helpMenuLanguage>
Select the application language.

It is highly recommended to exit and start again Ahtan Mobile to make sure all changes are accurate.
  </helpMenuLanguage>
  <helpMenuLocalTime>
This window allows you to correct possible gap between real prayer times and the ones given, which may occurs particularly if your phone use a specific time zone different from your country, or if DST (Summer time) is on during winter or vice versa.

Hour format is related to the way prayer times are displayed in the main screen.
  </helpMenuLocalTime>
  <helpMenuLocation>
This window allows you to change the location saved in the configuration.

There are two different ways of modifying your location :
- Manually if you know the GPS coordinates of your city.
- By searching your city from its name (or region name) if your phone subscription gives you access to Internet.
  </helpMenuLocation>
  <helpMenuPrayers>
This window allows you to display or to hide from the main screen the two ritual hours Imsak and Chourouk.
  </helpMenuPrayers>
  <!-- Errors -->
</strings>
